weddingstar.com 2017-12-14

# Weddingstar

Free Shipping On Orders Over $99 *North America Only



**Free Shipping Details:**   
Please note the following exceptions will apply: 

  * Free shipping applies to order within North America only (USA, Canada)
  * Orders that are considered remote as determined by FEDEX will be shown a remote fee at checkout 

Weddingstar Inc. knows you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust that we'll do so carefully and sensibly. This notice describes our privacy policy. By visiting our corporate, catalog, or partnership sites, you're accepting the practices described in this Privacy Notice.

  1. COLLECTION OF INFORMATION  

Personally identifiable information or personal information is defined as information that identifies you, as an individual, and includes your name, home address, home telephone number, and e-mail address. We only collect personally identifiable information about you after you have specifically and knowingly provided such information to us. By voluntarily providing this information to us at various points when using our Site(s), including, completing an order transaction, signing up as an Weddingstar Partner, or using the "Tell-A-Friend" feature that is posted on our Site(s), you will be consenting to the collection and use of your personal information by us for that online activity. You are under no obligation to provide us with this information and can access many aspects of the Site(s) without providing us any personal information.   

  2. THE PURPOSE OF OUR COLLECTING INFORMATION FROM YOU   

If you participate in an online activity, your personal information will only be used for the purposes of that online activity. Your email address and other information will NOT be resold to any third parties.  

  3. NON PERSONAL INFORMATION   

We constantly seek to maintain the integrity of, and make improvements to, the Site(s). As part of these efforts, we collect and analyze non-personally identifiable information. This information that does not identify you personally, but becomes available to us as a result of your visit to our Site(s). This information includes; your IP address, a number automatically assigned your computer when you visit the Site(s); your Internet Service Provider; and your Web Browser. We may also keep a record of which pages of the Site you visit, and how long you spend on each page. One way we use this non-personal information is as a diagnostic and administrative tool for identifying system problems and administering the Site. Our Site(s) makes use of cookies. Cookies are used to identify your order as you make purchases on our Site(s). If you have cookies disabled, you will not be able to make purchases with our Site(s). In this case, please contact our customer service desk for alternate ordering methods. We collect personal and non-personal information in a non-identifying, anonymous and aggregate form to enhance our Site design and for statistical purposes. These statistics and reports will contain only aggregated and no personally identifiable information. 

  4. LINKAGES  

Where links to Weddingstar Partner Web pages are provided, Weddingstar Inc. is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of those sites.   

  5. LISTS  

Weddingstar Inc. does not sell, give or trade its contact lists. Your email address and other information will NOT be resold to any third parties.
